<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.1.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-11-05T05:58:42-05:00</updated><id>/</id><title>One City Explorer</title><subtitle>Julian&#39;s travel blog around the world</subtitle><entry><title>Christmas in Switzerland</title><link href="/switzerland/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Christmas in Switzerland" /><published>2016-12-24T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2016-12-24T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/switzerland</id><content type="html" xml:base="/switzerland/">&lt;p&gt;Over the winter break, I’ve been given the opportunity to go to Europe for Christmas. The original plan was to finish my exams early and fly straight to Zurich followed by Interlaken. Unfortunately all my exams were very late so I missed out on Zurich. I will be back to explore Zurich!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In short, I fell in love with Switzerland. There’s just something about this country that just feels surreal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I landed in Zuirch and then caught the train straight to Interlaken. It was a two hour journey that was both smooth and comfortable. By the time I arrive, it was already dark. The hotel I was staying at was a short five minute walk from the train station. I basically spent the first night here exploring this small town.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2016/ZRH/Interlaken.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Interlaken&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;centerdid-you-know-switzerland-has-four-offical-languages-center&quot;&gt;&lt;center&gt;Did you know Switzerland has four offical languages? &lt;/center&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;center&gt;They are German, French, Italian, and Romansh
&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2016/ZRH/Train.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Train&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the second day, I headed to Jungfraujoch. Nicknamed, the Top of Europe, it is located on the Bernese Alps and  sits at an elevation of 3,466 metres. The journey from Interlaken involved about three different trains. The first train got me to Lauterbrunnen where I changed to a cog wheel driven train which brought me up to, an elevation of 2,061 metres, Kleine Scheidegg. The last 45 minutes of the train ride was in a tunnel that finally ended at Jungfraujoch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon reaching the observatory, it was just pure white outside with the howls of the wind. I still wanted to go outside to experience it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2016/ZRH/jfj.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;MeOnTopofEurope&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you can see, there actually wasn’t much to see. Yet knowing you’re practically standing in a cloud and on top of Europe, there’s no other feeling like it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They also had an ice palace up here. Everything here was made of ice, from the sculptures you see, and to the ground you walk on. Guess you can say it was pretty cool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2016/ZRH/Ice1.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;TopofEurope&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2016/ZRH/PolarBear.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;MeOnTopofEurope&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;centerpolar-bears-are-my-favourite-animals-center&quot;&gt;&lt;center&gt;Polar Bears are my favourite animals! &lt;/center&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This day ended up pretty much with a swiss classic food. Fondue! Authentic Swiss fondue. Can’t beat it with anything else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2016/ZRH/Christmas.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Christmas&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;centermerry-christmas-center&quot;&gt;&lt;center&gt;Merry Christmas! &lt;/center&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the last day in Switzerland, I did nothing but Ski! I can’t say much about it but it was very fun and I definetly do want to go back for more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2016/ZRH/Ski.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Ski&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!----&gt;</content><category term="Travel" /><category term="Europe" /><summary>Over the winter break, I’ve been given the opportunity to go to Europe for Christmas. The original plan was to finish my exams early and fly straight to Zurich followed by Interlaken. Unfortunately all my exams were very late so I missed out on Zurich. I will be back to explore Zurich!</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="{&quot;feature&quot;=&gt;&quot;/2016/ZRH/swiss_head.jpg&quot;}" /></entry></feed>
